BRAYAN MONTAÑO BELTRE

React Developer

I'm a software developer from the Dominican Republic, focused on Front-end & Web Development.

I work bringing designs alive and creating systems that allow users to digest the information and guide them in an immersive experience.

SKILLS

Javascript, React, Nextjs, HTML, CSS, Docker, GIT, Nodejs, TailwindCSS, Booststrap, Graphql, Wordpress, SquareSpace.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-End Developer

Oficina Gubernamental de Tecnologías de la Información y Comunicación (OGTIC) 2021 – Present

// Dominican Republic Government Site - www.gob.do

It was achieved that all the country's services are standardized through a digital platform, thus achieving transparency and reducing the time to carry out government processes.

// National Scholarship System - Beca Tu Futuro

Creation of the portal <u>becas.gob.do</u> used by more than 200,000 Dominican and international citizens to apply for national and international scholarships. Development of the back-office used by dozens of institutions in the Dominican Republic to create, configure, manage, publish and approve scholarships for citizens who apply for them.

// Datos Abiertos

Portal that uses an integrated API offered by the DMS CKAN to show the open data of the institutions of the Dominican Republic.

// Other projects

E-ticket, Censo, Observatorio MAP, Botón Verde, Sistema de Diseño Dominicano.

UI Engineer

Contract 2019 - 2021

// Benchmarking, research and information architecture, as well as review and prototyping for user testing.

IT Support Specialist

Alorica 2021

// I gained experience working with the IT department of a large multinational company.

Web Developer

Freelance 2019 - Present

// Websites development using React, WordPress, Squarespace, Webflow and Django.

EDUCATION

Software Engineering

Software Technologist

Universidad APEC (UNAPEC) 2019 – Present

Las Americas Institute of Technology (ITLA) 2017 - 2018

WORK REFERENCES

Ivan Firestone

Software Development Lead Oficina Presidencial de Tecnología de la Información y Comunicaciones 1 829 705 2424

Julissa Mateo

IT Director & Tech Consultant UNIBE - TOPTAL

1 809 796 6209